https://driftwood-dreams.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Who we are
Our website address is: http://driftwood-dreams.co.uk. Anita Russell is a sole trader and the artist.
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Order information like what was purchased, when it was purchased and where it should be sent
Customer information like your name, email address, and billing and shipping information
Personal details and photos to produce a likeness in the form of a papier mache sculpture
Photos may be used in publicity, marketing and development
The artist needs access to this information to help fulfill orders, process refunds and support you.
Comments
Currently there is no comments form. When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymised string created from your e-mail address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service Privacy Policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Media
Currently there is no way to leave images on the site.
If you were to upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.
Cookies
There is currently no log in on the site.
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt in to saving your name, e-mail address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics
The site is created in WordPress. WordPress does not collect any analytics data.
Who we share your data with
Your data is only shared with the Payment Processor PayPal, shipping providers and Driftwood-Dreams.
How long we retain your data
There is currently no registration on the site.
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognise and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
Your contact information
The business is owned by Anita Russell and is based in Richmond Surrey .
How we protect your data
Driftwood-Dreams.co.uk is a secure site and any computers used have data protection and virus software in place.
What data breach procedures we have in place
Any financial data is not held by us. All finances should go through PayPal.PayPal is safe for buyers, as the site platform is both secure and encrypted.
What third parties we receive data from
We accept payments through PayPal. When processing payments, some of your data will be passed to PayPal, including information required to process or support the payment, such as the purchase total and billing information.Please see the PayPal privacy policy for more details.
What automated decision making and/or profiling we do with user data
The web site does not provide a service which includes automated decision making . There is no aggregating of data for advertising. Information is purely used to create an artwork or process ad order.
Industry regulatory disclosure requirements
Anita Russell is not a  member of a regulated industry, or  subject to additional privacy laws.
